Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS 092
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Video and Film
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #1], 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0434)
      Content: Unedited, raw footage used for Eleventh Hour broadcast. David is interviewed and is seen observing art exhibition.
      TRT: 00:19:00
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #2], 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0437)
      TRT: 00:18:00
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #3], 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0440)
      TRT: 00:20:00
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #4], 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0443)
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #5], 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0446)
      TRT: 00:21:00
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #6], 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0449)
    - Eleventh Hour - broadcast, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0452)
      Content: Broadcast edit
    - Itsofomo #3 - Edit Master, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0414)
      TRT: 00:36:00
    - Itsofomo #4 - Edit Master, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0417)
      TRT: 00:33:00
    - Kitchen Tape I, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0402)
      TRT: 00:37:00
    - Kitchen Tape II, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0405)
      TRT: 00:34:00
    - Kitchen Tape III, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0408)
      TRT: 00:58:00
    - Kitchen Tape IV, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0411)
      TRT: 00:35:00
    - [Kitchen Tape 2 Production Element], [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0024)
      TRT: 00:54:15
    - [Kitchen Tape 3 Production Element], [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0028)
    - [Kitchen Tape 4 Production Element], [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0032)
    - Fear of Disclosure, The Psycho-social Implications of HIV Revelation, [1990] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0211)
      TRT: 00:05:30
      Original Format: BetacamSP
    - Fear of Disclosure, The Psycho-social Implications of HIV Revelation, [1990] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0068)
    - Black & White..., [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0384)
      TRT: 00:23:00
    - Fireworks..., [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0396)
      TRT: 00:41:00
    - Lesbians etc., History etc., [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0429)
      TRT: 00:32:00
    - Plain Ants..., [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0387)
      TRT: 00:27:00
    - Slo-Mo Blue Boys 1, [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0423)
      TRT: 00:22:00
    - Slo-Mo Blue Boys - 2, [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0426)
      TRT: 00:13:00
    - Slowed Master, [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0393)
    - Stock Images for Sec III Performance, [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0390)
      TRT: 00:11:00
    - Tape II Upstate, [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0399)
      TRT: 00:17:00
    - [Upstate w/ Marion Scemama Part 1], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0007)
      TRT: 01:30:00
    - [Upstate w/ Marion Scemama Part 2], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0009)
    - [Upstate Part 1], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0015)
    - [Upstate Part 2], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0017)
    - [Upstate Part 3], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0019)
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 1], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0061)
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 2], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0064)
      TRT: 00:08:50
    - [WOJO NEA #1], undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0455)
    - [WOJO NEA #2], undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0458)
    - [WOJO NEA #3], undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0461)
      TRT: 00:31:00
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Original Material
    This subseries contains completed works, works in progress, and source footage. Researcher access is limited to subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies. There may not be access material available for all original material. Please contact a Fales archivist for access.
    - [Animo; Bug; Little House], [1985] (Folder ID: 092.0001)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - [R+R/ Phil Zwickler], 1987 (Folder ID: 092.0077)
      TRT: [00:60:00]
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #1], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0036)
      Format: Betacam
      TRT: [00:20:00]
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #2], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0037)
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #3], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0038)
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #4], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0039)
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #5], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0040)
    - [Eleventh Hour; Art and AIDs #6], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0041)
    - Eleventh Hour - broadcast, [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0042)
    - [Interview w/ Artists Space and David Wojnarowicz], 1989 (Folder ID: 092.0046)
      TRT: 01:17:00
    - [Kitchen Tape 1 Production Element], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0023)
      TRT: 00:37:01
    - [Kitchen Tape 2 Production Element], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0027)
      TRT: 00:33:51
    - [Kitchen Tape 3 Production Element], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0031)
      TRT: 00:57:44
    - [Kitchen Tape 4 Production Element], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0035)
      TRT: 00:35:12
    - [ITSOFOMO #1], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0051)
    - [ITSOFOMO #2], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0052)
    - [ITSOFOMO #3], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0053)
    - [ITSOFOMO #4], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0055)
    - [ITSOFOMO #3 - Edit Master], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0054)
      TRT: 00:35:55
    - [ITSOFOMO #4 - Edit Master], [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0056)
      TRT: 00:32:51
    - [ITSOFOMO - Dat Xfer Workprint] (audio only), [1989] (Folder ID: 092.0057)
    - [Damned in the USA], 1991 (Folder ID: 092.0080)
      TRT: [00:68:00]
    - [Marion - Tape #1 Master], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0011)
    - [Upstate w/ Marion Scemama], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0012)
      Format: S-VHS
      TRT: 02:00:00
    - [Upstate], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0013)
    - [Upstate Tape 2], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0014)
      TRT: 00:16:48
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 1], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0060)
      TRT: [00:21:00]
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 2], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0063)
      TRT: [00:08:50]
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 1], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0066)
      TRT: 00:22:17
    - [Blue Boys Slo Mo 2], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0067)
    - [Lesbians, Globe Gun, Solar System, Indians, Ships...], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0074)
      TRT: 00:31:56
    - [Project: Red, Hot and Blue], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0075)
      TRT: 00:03:15
    - [Steve Brown/ David Wojnarowicz], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0059)
    - [Decomposed Animal, Earthquake, Commercials, NEA Controversy], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0078)
    - [G.I. Joe, Pulverizer, Robots, Evader, Arctic Blast], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0081)
    - [Making Plaster Heads], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0079)
    - [Son of Sam and Delilah], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0076)
    - [Plain Ants, Sex Ants, Target, Guns, Clock, Monkey, House... Bigots, Cathedral, Color American Flag], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0003)
    - [Stock Images for Sec. III Performance], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0004)
      TRT: 00:10:32
    - [Fireworks, Steer Wrestling, Wagon Wheel... Reagan, Bombs, Scorpion, Dust Feet], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0006)
      TRT: 00:40:59
    - [Black and White, Flag at Night, Los Angeles Muscle, etc.], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0002)
    - [Slowed Master], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0005)
      TRT: 00:20:23
    - [WOJO NEA #1], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0043)
      Format: Betacam SP
      TRT: [00:30:00]
    - [WOJO NEA #2], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0044)
    - [WOJO NEA #3], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0045)
  - Subseries C: Film - Access Copies
    - [Heroin - Unedited Color Footage], [circa 1979] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0175)
      Format: 16mm
      Footage: [290 ft.]
      Description:
    - Heroin, 1981 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0132)
      Footage: [92 ft.]
      TRT: [00:02:50]
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel III], [circa mid-1980s] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0203)
      Footage: [209 ft.]
    - [Mexico Film Footage II], [1983, 1986 as per Super8 edge code]] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0193)
      Footage: [179 ft.]
    - Mexico, etc... Peter, etc... [as per original container], [circa 1986, 1987] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0198)
      Footage: [405 ft.]
    - A Fire in My Belly, 1986-1987 (work in progress) (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0130)
      Footage: [470 ft.]
      TRT: [00:13:05]
    - [Mexico Film Footage], [1988 as per Super8 edge code] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0188)
      Footage: [736 ft.]
    - Beautiful People, 1988-1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0164)
      Footage: [1400 ft.]
      TRT: [00:38:00]
    - Beautiful People - B+W Extras (Out-takes and Alt. Titles), 1988-1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0166)
      Footage: [380 ft.]
      TRT: [00:11:00]
    - Beautiful People - Color Extras (Out-takes and Alt. Titles), 1988-1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0168)
      Footage: [335 ft.]
      TRT: [00:10:00]
    - [Footage for Film About Peter Hujar], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0135)
      Footage: [600 ft.]
      TRT: [00:12:00]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 6 super 8mm rolls
    - Where Evil Dwells, [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0139)
      Footage: [1150 ft.]
      TRT: [00:28:00]
    - [Howdy Doody #120], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0141)
      Footage: 330 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody #119], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0143)
      Footage: 659 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody #121], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0145)
      Footage: 706 ft.
    - [Swamp/Skeletons], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0169)
    - [Ants] (color), [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0171)
      TRT: 00:08:00
    - [Driving, Sky, and Misc. Shots], [undated] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 092.0173)
  - Subseries D: Film - Original Material
    This subseries contains completed works, works in progress, and source footage. Researcher access is limited to subseries C: Film - Access Copies. There may not be access material available for all original material. Please contact a Fales archivist for access.
    - Beautiful People, 1988-1989 (Folder ID: 092.0106)
      Format: Super8mm
      Footage: 504 ft.
    - Beautiful People - Out-takes (color), 1988-1989 (Folder ID: 092.0107)
      Footage: [66 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 3 Super8mm rolls
    - Beautiful People - Out-takes and Alt. Titles (B+W), 1988-1989 (Folder ID: 092.0108)
      Footage: [134 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 4 super8mm rolls
    - Beautiful People - Alt. Titles (color), 1988-1989 (Folder ID: 092.0109)
      Footage: [65 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 2 super8mm rolls
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel], [1988 as per edge code] (Folder ID: 092.0110)
      Footage: [363 ft.]
    - [Mexico Film Footage], [1988 as per edge code] (Folder ID: 092.0111)
      Footage: 386 ft.
    - [Mexico Film Footage II], [1983, 1986 as per edge code] (Folder ID: 092.0112)
      Footage: 74 ft.
    - Mexico, etc... Peter, etc... [as per container], [circa 1986, 1987] (Folder ID: 092.0113)
      Footage: [225 ft.]
    - Fear of Disclosure, The Psycho-social Implications of HIV Revelation, 1988 (Folder ID: 092.0114)
      Footage: [210 ft.]
      TRT: [00:05:00]
    - Where Evil Dwells - Camera Original I, [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0115)
      Footage: [400 ft.]
    - Where Evil Dwells - Camera Original II, [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0116)
    - [New York Cultural Centre Annex Performance], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0117)
      Footage: 263 ft.
    - [Rolls 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0118)
      Footage: 401 ft. 49 frames
    - [Rolls 9,10,11], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0119)
      Footage: 149 ft. 70 frames
    - [Rolls 17,18,19], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0120)
      Footage: 150 ft. 46 frames
    - [Anti-Gay Bigots, Misc Footage], [1986 as per edge code] (Folder ID: 092.0121)
      Footage: 149 ft.
    - [Frog Dance, etc.], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0122)
      Footage: 522 ft.
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel III], [circa mid-1980s] (Folder ID: 092.0123)
      Footage: 93 ft. 35 frames
    - A Fire in My Belly, [circa 1985] (Folder ID: 092.0124)
      Footage: 262 ft. 24 frames
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel], [late 1980s] (Folder ID: 092.0125)
      Footage: 206 ft. 65 frames
    - [Howdy Doody Footage I], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0126)
      Footage: 360 ft. 66 frames
    - [Howdy Doody Footage II], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0127)
      Footage: 202 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody Footage III], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0128)
      Footage: 388 ft.
    - Heroin, 1981 (Folder ID: 092.0133)
      Footage: 51 ft.
    - [Peter Hujar - Rolls], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0136)
      Footage: [350 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 6 super8mm rolls
    - [Heroin - Unedited Color Footage], [circa 1979] (Folder ID: 092.0146)
      Footage: [340 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 7 super8mm rolls
    - [Cockfights], [1986] (Folder ID: 092.0147)
      Footage: [175 ft.]
    - [Out Sarah's Window; Demolition Derby], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0148)
    - [Nature, Water, Swamp], [1987] (Folder ID: 092.0149)
      Footage: [425 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 9 super8mm rolls
    - [Rain/Mammals], [1981,1987] (Folder ID: 092.0150)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 10 super8mm rolls
    - [Gorillas, Elephants, Waves, Sky], [1986,1987] (Folder ID: 092.0151)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 7 super8mm rolls]
    - [Cavern Point/Driving Shots], [1987, 1983] (Folder ID: 092.0152)
      Footage: [275 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 5 super8mm rolls
    - [Misc. B+W Shots], [1983,1986,1987] (Folder ID: 092.0153)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 8 super8mm rolls
    - [Ants] (color), [1986,1987,1988] (Folder ID: 092.0154)
      Footage: [160 ft.]
    - [Swamp/Skeleton] (color), [1985, unknown] (Folder ID: 092.0155)
      Footage: [240 ft.]
    - [Driving, Sky, and Misc. Shots], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0155)
    - [Fire Boys, Ants, and Mexico Themes], [1981,1984,1986,1987] (Folder ID: 092.0157)
      Footage: [300 ft.]
    - [Unidentified Film w/ David Wojnarowicz], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0158)
      Footage: 128 ft.
    - [Nite Scenes w/ David W.(Neg); Centaur Films], [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0159)
      Footage: 102 ft. 6 frames
    - Manhattan Love Suicides, 1984 (Folder ID: 092.0212)
      Format: [Super8mm]
      Footage: [unknown]
      Description: Featurette
    - [Aeroport/ Train Lines/ Gary/ Rail Landscapes/ Bercy] (undeveloped film reel), [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0213)
    - [Crows] (undeveloped film reel), [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0214)
    - [Bercy Windows, Stones/ Fire] (undeveloped film reel), [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0215)
    - [A) Morphologies, Restaurant Cafe 2] (undeveloped film reel), [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0216)
    - [B) Morphologies, Restaurant Cafe 2] (undeveloped film reel), [undated] (Folder ID: 092.0217)
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 90, undated (Box 90)
      092.0106-092.0123
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 91, undated (Box 91)
      092.0124-092.0128, 092.0133, 092.0136, 092.0146-092.0149 C
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 92, undated (Box 92)
      092.0149 D-092.0154
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 93, undated (Box 93)
      092.0155-092.0157, 092.0160, 092.0162, plus 7 unnumbered folders
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 94, undated (Box 94)
      092.0012-092.0013, 092.0042
  - Subseries E: Commercial Works by Others
    - Anita Dances of Vice, by Rosa von Praunheim, VHS tape (Dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Bayard Rustin, by Phil Zwickler, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - The Critical Years / The Grace of God, by Gerald Lecuyer, 40 min. VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Excerpts from: Blind Prosperity / Money Talk, by Gloria McLean & Ben Neill, Teliospore, by Gloria McLean, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Fedora / Laura, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Fingered, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Game Set Match, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Genet / Harvey Milk, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, Twentieth Century Fox, VHS tape, undated (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - How to Marry a Millionaire, Twentieth Century Fox, VHS tape, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - How to Shoot a Crime, by Kraus, (Chris?) 26 min. VHS tape, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - La Belle et La Bete / Visages de Femmes, VHS tape, undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - La Dolce Vita, Pt. I, by Federico Fellini, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - La Dolce Vita, Pt. II, by Federico Fellini, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Lawrence of Arabia, Columbia Pictures, Pts. 1-2, 2 VHS tapes, undated (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Manhattan love Suicides w/ Bill Rice & D. Wojnarowicz, b&w, 30 min. VHS tape, undated (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Maria Callas: Hamburg Concert 1959, Kuktur, VHS (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Mondo Cane / Macbeth (Kurosawa) / Sting in Tokyo, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Mother Theresa, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Mr. Hulot's Holiday, by Jacques Tati, & other video, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Never on Sunday, MGM, UA, VHS tape, undated (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Pursuit of Happiness (Malle) / La Strada / Stranger Than Paradise, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Quilt, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - The Red Hot Organization / No Alternative, Nov 1993, VHS tape (dub) (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Red Hot & Blue: A Tribute to Cole Porter to Benefit AIDS Research and Relief, Arista, 1990, VHS tape (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Rev. Howard Finster, Man of Vision, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - The Right Side of My Brain, by Richard Kern, 30 min. VHS tape, undated (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Rumblefish, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Sex vs. Guns, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, undated (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Stop the Church, by Robert Hilferty, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Submit to Me / Death Valley '69 / You Killed Me First, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Submit to Me / Death Valley '69 / You Killed Me First, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Tom Rubnitz, Video Director: various, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - A Virus Knows No Morals, by Rosa von Praunheim, First Run Features, 84 minute VHS tape, undated (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Where Evil Dwells, by Wojnarowicz & Turner, VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - The Young Ones (various series episodes), VHS tape (dub), undated (Box 97, Folder 36)
- Series XI: Art Works
  - Subseries A: Finished/Original
    - Art - color separation, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Art Sketch Book - "Bowery Joe", undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Art - 2 prints - Brain-Time, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Art - production - color sample - The Death of American Spirituality, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Art - production - color separation - The Death of American Spirituality, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Art - black ink, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Art - frottage, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Art - images and text, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Art - blue ballpoint pen drawing - "Look Honey a Hallucination", undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Art - Xerox diptych, undated (Box 19, Folder 9A.)
    - Art - "Mexico" collage, undated (Box 19, Folder 9B.)
    - Art - "I Have Always Liked...the Idea of Movies. .", undated (Box 19, Folder 9C.)
    - Art and Images - Memories that Smell Like Gasoline, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Art and Poem - graphite pencil drawing of dog with cast, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Art - Peter Hujar's diagnostic letter altered with a drawing of two men kissing, from W's "Fuck You Faggot-Hater" series, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Art - transparency, "Buying Souls. .", undated (Box 19, Folder 12A.)
    - Comic collage, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Comic - altered Archie comic: "Yo Sadie. .", undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Comic - altered Archie comic: "Reggie is trying to kick his junk habit again. .", undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Comic - altered Archie comic: "Archie and Mr. Weatherbee in 'School Tool'" (Box 19, Folder 15A.)
    - Folder with sperm art - painted collage on manilla folder, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Image - brain, eye, earth, heart, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Images, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Man's face in shadow, undated (Box 19, Folder 18A.)
    - Postcard - altered, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Rimbaud mask, undated (Box 90)
      Rehoused and removed from Box 19 Folder 20 to Box 90
    - Sperm/Money/Seeds w/envelope, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Stencils - Burning House and Falling Man (removed for special housing), undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Subseries B: Drawings
    - Bee: "I'm gonna hold my breath until I die", undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bellevue Hospital, sketches from, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bread loaf sewn, ape with club, etc., undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Crashing dove, large deer with leg through roof of house, etc., undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Fuck You Bozo, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - recordings after sleep, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Two men with trousers down, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Water, drawings from, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Various drawings, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: Sketches
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sketchpad, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Storyboard for Times Square Project, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material
    - Ads in Spanish, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Archives of American Art materials, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Article on bullfrog, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Article on prison in Newsweek (Oct. 6, 1986) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Autumn leaf cut-outs, undated (Box 19, Folder 4A.)
    - Cards, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Cards - French, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Cards - pictures of animals, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Cards - postcards and envelopes, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Cards - postcards (may contain notes), undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Cards - postcards, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Clippings and tearsheets, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Comics, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Ripley's Believe it or Not Collection, A Guide, 1978. (Box 19, Folder 14A.)
    - Exploded Views, Completely Detailed Drawings of Famous Firearms, undated (Box 19, Folder 14B.)
    - Comics, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Comics, undated (Box 20, Folder 15A.)
    - Comics, undated (Box 20, Folder 15B.)
    - Comics, undated (Box 20, Folder 15C.)
    - Comics, undated (Box 20, Folder 15D.)
    - Coupons, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Decals, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Diagram of eye, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Diagram of frog, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Envelopes, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Flag images on felt, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Holograms, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Maps, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Maps, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Maps, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Maps, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Mexican wrestling magazines, undated (Box 20, Folder 26A.)
    - Night Train label, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Plastic rulers, undated (Box 20, Folder 28A.)